Valmiki! Is your wife here?
Yes...
Where is Mr. Ramachandra’s wife?
She’s here.
It’s a baby boy.
That’s great news.
I don’t have change… I can’t
afford to tip you a note.
Thank God.
Sister, clean the baby
and put her to bed.
We must inform
Mr. Ramachandra about this.
Note down the exact time.
I don’t want the
horoscope to be messed up.
It’s 12...
Sir, I need the phone.
Can’t you see that
I’m talking here?
It’s an emergency, sir.
Mr. Ramachandra’s baby boy…
So what?
He was stable when the
doctor saw him last.
But he’s not moving now.
Ma’am is under sedation.
I’ll call you back.
Doctor informed the family
that it’s a baby boy.
I’m worried.
They are influential people.
I’m afraid they
will pin this on me.
Fine.
I’m blessed with a boy.
Let’s switch Mr. Ramachandra’s
son with mine.
I'm working in their company.
It’s their generosity
that I lead a decent life.
This is the least
I can do for them.
I’ll give them my baby boy.
How will you explain
this to your wife?
Only my family will
prosper if he is with us.
But a whole community will
prosper if he is with them.
I will sacrifice my child.
By God’s grace, hopefully I’ll
have another kid in a year or so.
Sir, listen to me.
Don’t say a word…
just come with me.
Come on.
Pick him up.
We are switching dead
baby with a baby.
What’s wrong? Pick him up.
Make it fast.
Let’s get out, come on.
Let’s go!
Look.
He's alive.
Give the baby to me.
-Give him to me!
-Sir, no!
Shut up!
No, sir.
You did sacrifice your kid.
But now you are betraying them.
Betrayal?
Ramachandra and I joined this
company at the same time.
We’d go to the office
together on my scooter.
He got lucky and married ARK’s
daughter and drives a car now.
What about me?
And I’m still driving
the same old scooter.
He just got lucky.
This baby though...
he could’ve cried when we
switched him with my son.
He started crying when
we got downstairs. Why?
He is unlucky.
My son is destined to
lead a superior life...
while his son leads
an ordinary life.
It’s God’s play...
there’s nothing I can do about it.
-Go away!
-No, sir. Don’t do it.
This is not betrayal...
it’s a sin.
You had an evil plan in mind.
-I can’t let you do this.
-Shut up!
-Don't separate the baby from his mother.
-I said shut up!
I won’t let you do this.
Give the baby to me.
I said let go!
Don’t make a scene now.
It’s over!
Forget it and go away.
-Give the baby back to me.
-I said go away!
Hey, Valmiki!
It's a baby boy.
How about you?
Baby boy or baby girl?
Baby boy!
What’s wrong?
Nothing. I got a cramp.
You got lucky, man.
What’s his name?
Raj Infra!
Amazing!
Did you like it?
It’s a royal name, sir.
The name a King deserves.
This is all good.
But have you thought of
any names for your son?
Yes.
Tell me.
Is that a name?
Is this "the" name?
Yeah!
What kind of name is this?
I’ve performed several ceremonies.
But I will never
approve of such a name.
I’ll be putting my image
at stake with this name.
-Priest...
-What?
How can you call your son "Bantu"?
It’s disgusting!
Right!
Why? Lord Hanuman is
called "Rama Bantu."
He’s still worshipped.
Lord Hanuman and Lord
Rama are an exception.
Whose servant is
your son going to be?
What is this?
You scored nine in Math?
It’s okay if your teacher didn’t give
you a higher score. We’ll add it.
Seven...
-What are you doing, Valmiki?
-Ma’am...
Raj’s progress report.
Oh. His score in Math?
97.
Dear! He scored 98 in Math.
Why did you leave
those two marks?
You should’ve scored a 100.
How can you say that, dear?
He got such a good score.
His score won’t change anything.
Few people are born that way.
Very bad!
Hey, stop it!
Hold it properly.
Thank God! He’s here and
my son is in the palace.
He’s happy even while sleeping.
Even though you lost everything,
How do you manage to stay happy?
Hey!
Grandma has sent some pickle.
You need to go get it.
Go to the bus stand.
Do I have an option?
Here you go, dear.
Coconut and camphor.
-Where’s the pumpkin?
-We don’t have it.
-Did you add it to the lentil soup?
-I did, sir.
He is coming home from
America after two years.
We need pumpkin
to ward off evil.
Damn it!
He isn’t coming home
after a great achievement.
He dropped out in the
final semester of MBA.
Please calm down, sir.
Really?
-Hey! Are you at the bus stand?
-Yes.
Yes, you told me
to collect pickles.
Dump them, buy a pumpkin and
come to Mr. ARK’s residence.
Pumpkin?
Yes! Pumpkin!
How will I get a pumpkin here?
-Pumpkin?
-Don’t be late. It’s urgent.
Autorickshaw!
Wait here.
Hey! Hey! Where are you rushing?
You can’t carry it.
I’m carrying your burden.
This is nothing.
Give it to me.
I’ve been noticing it
since I was a kid.
You never let me cross the gate.
What’s your problem?
It’s Vaikunthapuram, son.
No entry for losers like you.
Few lives don’t get any better.
Go back home.
Raj is here! Raj is here!
He has affection towards
everyone except me.
Sir, should I drop
the luggage inside?
Why would I hire an auto,
if I had such a big house.
Let's go...
let’s drive through the
bumpy lanes of Ameerpet.
That’s our range.
Have you been drinking
a lot in America?
You are shining.
Well, he’s back.
You both can drink together now.
What did you get me?
He’s already feeling low, Dad.
Don’t hurt him more, please!
But we are hurt, not him.
Dad, I have to do some shopping.
Take me with you
while going to office.
I’m busy… he will take you.
What is she saying?
She says he’s got an interview.
It’s eight o'clock now.
His interview is at ten.
Ask him to take her along
and buy medicines for his mom.
And then attend the interview.
He has plenty of time on his hands.
Not again.
What is she saying now?
How can he manage in
such a short span of time?
Like I manage this
family with my salary.
Ask him to do the same.
-Hey!
-Yes.
We are from a middle-class family.
We have tons of
things to worry about.
-We have to move on.
-Okay.
SIRI LADIES' TAILOR.
Brother!
Brother.
Buy medicines for mom.
I’m running late for my interview.
-They snatched my scarf?
-I know, right?
If girls like the color,
they will snatch it.
What will men do with a scarf?
They must be out of their minds.
Buy chocolates with the change.
Usually, brothers get very angry and fight
when men misbehave with their sisters.
You have way too many
expectations from me, sweetheart.
I’m late for my interview.
Would you react like this,
if it were your girlfriend?
No.
Get lost!
Damn! That was provoking.
I feel like doing something now.
Brother, did you see a gang pass
by with a scarf in their hands?
The guys on the red bike?
Don't try to act smart with me.
Where did they go?
Brother...
That scarf...
belongs to my sister.
Your sister looks smoking hot, man.
Can I get the scarf back?
Get your sister here in
exchange for the scarf.
Scarf...
Give me the scarf!
When he said my sister looks
hot, I didn’t feel bad.
She’s a beautiful girl.
I was happy that she’d save
some money on the dowry.
That’s how we think.
But that guy intervened
like some villain.
And said sister in exchange for the scarf.
How could he say that?
No, listen...
he ripped my heart apart.
Looking up and to the sides
when I’m sad is my mannerism.
But you don’t have the basic sense of
thinking twice before hitting someone.
-Hey, sis.
-Sorry brother… I got angry.
That’s fine.
I got your scarf back.
-They gave it back?
-Yes, they cleaned it as well.
Awesome!
That move?
Stylish, right?
I like it as well.
I don’t know… it
just worked out.
Why do you want to join
our tourism company?
With the help of your company
I can visit countries.
He's energetic.
Give me your file.
I deal with sales
in this company.
But the HR met with
a small accident.
He’ll be joining us later.
So, let’s proceed.
Hey! I like your sense of
humor, man.
Okay, let's read some more.
People usually visit
Bangkok or buy the Bentley car.
But you have written,
"I want to buy a bike."
-Have you got time to spare, sir?
-Lots of it.
-Dear...
-Yes.
His college is starting tomorrow.
Did you bring him any new clothes?
Of course, I did.
I said Mr. Ramachandra’s son
that Bantu was starting college.
He gave me all his old
clothes right away.
That’s not it...
I was looking at the perfume in his hand.
Was he gracious enough to
give his perfume as well?
Ae you kidding me?
Do you want it or not?
Do you have something to say?
I was forced to.
You’re always so blunt
and honest, right?
I get a headache whenever I lie.
And when I started speaking the truth… the
other person started having a headache.
I feel so relaxed now, sir.
So, you must’ve started telling the
truth about the little things first.
Not at all, sir.
I had gone straight for the big fish.
Hey! I guess it’s the loan shark.
Tell him I’m not home.
Hey... is your father's home?
Father...
He asked me to tell
you he isn’t home.
So shameless!
How could you make
your kid lie for you?
You’ve already lost
one of your legs.
Betray a good man like me
and you’ll lose the other one as well.
Whatever.
That leg is going to hurt badly.
What did you just tell him?
Better, you should’ve
led him to me directly.
You’re just supposed to say,
"Dad’s not home." That’s it!
Hey, can I see your dad?
He’s not home...
Why do we care if he’s behind
the wall or under the table?
He’s not home and that’s final.
Your wife is not home, right?
Shameless fellow.
Hey!
We are a middle-class family.
How will you deal with life
if you can’t lie?
Hey, you’re always busy cooking.
Get some sense into him.
Besides,
you’re not Ramachandra’s son.
You can’t afford to speak the truth
always. Moreover, aren’t you afraid?
If I tell the truth,
I’ll be afraid only for that moment.
But if I lie,
I’ll be afraid all the time.
That was a great punch!
You rocked!
A mother is in pain only
when she’s giving birth.
But a father’s in pain
throughout the kid’s life.
Hey! Why are you not clapping?
He has fans and they
clapped for him.
You have none and
so you get nothing.
Sit down and eat.
-You got a seat in MBA.
-It was a prestigious college, sir.
Why did you give it up?
Hey! The job is done.
I sorted everything out.
Sort?
How could you cancel his
scholarship to get her a seat?
He’s a man.
He’ll figure something out.
What are you looking at?
Son...
Shall I tell you something?
You might have scored 90+ runs.
But your number of centuries
still stands at zero.
That explains your
life to the dot.
You almost get what you want
but never quite have it.
Like I told you,
few lives don’t get any better.
This tragedy calls for
more than a century, Bantu.
Shall we try something musical?
Something light-hearted.
Hey! Give the table lamp and desk
to your sister. She has to study.
My son is always a King.
I can’t begin to tell you my story
My pain has no ending
Why are these dads torturing us?
They don’t listen to us or understand us
When I think of dad
It gives me chills all over
I ask for 100 bucks and
He reminds me we’re not rich
I cry to myself thinking
He’s out of his mind
It’s the same scene in every household.
What do you say, bro?
My name is Bantu
And I hate my name
I fight with my cunning dad
Day and night
My mother’s husband...
Turned out to be my dad
You can’t lock rain in a bottle
You can’t capture joy in a snap
There are no shortcuts to freedom
You can deny me or
Join hands with me
You can’t fit the woods in your backyard
You can’t make a pigeon your paperweight
You can’t start a bonfire using a volcano
I’m a blank cheque that’s not cashed
Being the son of Valmiki means
Being the epitome of problems
Only Thanos can make people
Smile with a snap
My mother’s husband...
He’s one big dummy
He wants a new bike.
He can use my scooter.
That’s enough, son.
He gets emotional
for small things.
Enough… let me go.
No, you are safe here.
I might hit you,
if you are far from me.
Bantu, after listening to your
story, I feel like killing your dad.
But it’s a huge risk.
It also makes me want to
adopt you and send you abroad.
But it’s a costly affair.
Because I can’t do either of it.
Let me offer you this job.
Come on, dear. Sign here.
This should end
all your miseries.
Sekhar is here.
Great timing!
He’s our HR. Meet him and
make a good first impression.
I’ll impress him, sir.
What happened?
I was happy you got the job.
but I’m shocked you hit the HR.
This is the time to put your character,
integrity and individuality aside...
and say sorry.
Mr. Reddy...
-Hey! What are you doing here?
-Get out!
I’m begging you.
Please, sir... I’m begging you.
I really need this
job sir… come on.
I’ll give you the job... I feel like
I’m going to puke. Stop it right now.
You will stand by your
word, right?
Yes, let go of me!
Sign here… right here.
Right here, sir.
That's it!
Hey, he signed it! But how?
I touched his feet
like you said.
-What did he do?
-He signed my papers.
I will catch him.
Go downstairs.
I’ll come join you.
Did he hit you hard?
He hit me with a
scarf but it was...
I won’t say the word.
But he broke my heart, Reddy.
No matter what you say,
I believe he has no ego.
-That is why he touched your feet.
-What about me?
You have no common sense.
That is why you snatched
his sister’s scarf.
I didn’t snatch it, Reddy.
It got stuck on my hand.
I didn’t mean to do it.
It was an accident.
You could’ve returned the scarf.
-I didn’t want to create a scene.
-Well, you already did.
-Why is the production on hold?
-No stock, sir.
Then order it.
The distribution has been halted
because we didn’t pay the bills, sir.
Call the bank and clear the due.
The OD is already too high.
I will take care of it.
-Which floor?
-Where are you going?
-Ninth floor.
-Me too.
Yeah. Yeah.
I’ve never seen you around.
I joined yesterday.
-Yesterday?
-Yes. Yesterday.
Have you met your boss?
He didn’t come to
office yesterday.
Yeah. Yeah. Thank you.
This looks good as well.
I saw a girl in the
elevator earlier.
She blew my mind.
Is she the receptionist,
Mr. Reddy?
I’d be with her right now
if she was so beautiful.
Go and greet our boss first.
We can relax for the day.
Relax and chill!
I’ll impress her and be right back.
Now what did you do?
Hey! I thought you were just
in the elevator with ma’am.
But you were trying
to get on her.
I won’t say the word.
You were trying to flirt with her, right?
What do we do, Mr. Reddy?
You had a problem
yesterday as well.
I gave you a solution
and it worked out.
You want me to touch her feet?
Any other alternatives?
He doesn’t just hold legs… he twists
them according to his convenience.
Come in.
You think the name Bantu is cute?
It’s disgusting, ma’am.
In the elevator earlier...
Hello...
Look up.
My eyes are up here.
It’s hard for me, ma’am.
You’re working under me.
And I’m happy about it, ma’am.
-Only the cabin has changed.
-I still have to touch people’s feet.
Telling the truth is my first
nature, ma’am.
Sadism is my mannerism, Bantu.
What?
Do people come here for a vacation?
Maybe they can eat
without cooking.
Hey, listen.
Hey.
Why don't you change the topic?
I'm bored.
What?
Why are you guys just leaving?
That’s the only thing
on your mind, right?
-Who’s this?
-It’s me, ma’am.
Who are you?
You got upset with me for staring
at your legs in the lift.
And so, you sent me to Kutch.
It’s me. Bantu.
I haven’t seen a fellow
human being in three days.
And this couple is lost in love.
Oh, my God!
This guy is pulling
out the camping tents.
The temperature here is blazing, ma’am.
Please do something.
What?
Okay, I’ll do it.
Stop crushing her.
Hey, ma'am. Stop!
It’s very steep…
you will fall.
I’ll set up a rope and you
can grab it and go down.
Don’t grab him. Grab the rope.
Wow! He is dancing so well.
Who is it?
It’s me, ma’am.
These people think I am dancing
but I am shivering.
They are uploading the
videos on the internet, ma’am.
Just give me a corner
seat in our office.
I’ll be at your feet.
I don't understand
your fantasy with legs.
I didn’t mean it like
that, ma’am.
I’m begging you.
Are you sleeping?
Good. Sleep.
I bought you 24 apples per
year, two per month.
So that makes 600 apples
in the last 25 years.
It's pointless.
You are not conscious.
You don’t eat.
I have diabetes... I can’t eat.
This leg keeps bothering me.
When we fought for the baby
in the hospital that day...
I had a cramp, remember?
It just got worse with
time and now I’m limping.
You got lucky...
you are in coma for so long.
Because it happened on
the day my son was born.
Mr. Ramachandra is continuing
your treatment against all odds.
So, don’t feel guilty about it.
How long will you...
-Do you speak Telugu?
-What?
I mean to say... Malayalam.
How long will you
cling on to this body?
Just let go.
Take my advice and die in peace.
Did you check her
blood pressure?
Where is the nurse?
I want her reports.
Put the oxygen mask on.
Is she going to live?
Probably for two years
if she’s in coma.
She has two more months.
-Can she see?
-It’s complicated.
-Can she hear us?
-I’m not sure.
-Can she talk?
-Impossible!
Thank you.
You act cranky under the sun.
And you shiver in the snow.
You call me off the
hook and say "Ma’am..."
You’re good for nothing.
Few lives don’t get any
better, do they?
What?
Don’t belittle my life, ma’am.
I’ve heard enough from my dad.
I would get really
angry when he says it.
But now that you’re
also saying it...
I’m afraid it might be true.
Over all these years,
I’ve never had a single
phenomenal day in my life.
Is bad luck riding my
dad, me or my life?
I don't know.
Ma'am, this is a request.
Please wear pants
and longer skirts.
I can’t look away.
So beautiful, ma’am.
Get up.
When there’s weight on your
head, you won't look down.
-Ma’am?
-You can observe it, Bantu.
True.
You will know it very soon.
If you work hard,
you will succeed.
Go.
Work on the Paris tour.
Look.
She’s ma’am!
We know she’s our ma’am.
What's next?
Ma’am was saying...
Sekhar, we have to handle
a few things with love.
Then do it.
-Dear...
-Yes, dear.
For the first time today...
I looked into her eyes
instead of staring at her legs.
Ma’am, my foot!
Sekhar, handle with love.
He’s already in love with her.
My eyes are hooked on to your legs
Don’t step on my gaze, show me some mercy
My dreams will guard your eyes like kohl
You set me on fire when
You rub your rosy cheeks
Your tresses fly as my breath
Whistles in the air
Don’t get all cranky
And push me away
Sweetheart!
I can’t help but fall for you
You know how the heart
Sways to the youth’s beat
Sweetheart!
I can’t help but fall for you
You know how the heart
Sways to the youth’s beat
My eyes are hooked on to your legs
Don’t step on my gaze, show me some mercy
You’re like the cool breeze
Spilling fragrances of jasmine
You’re like the land
Shimmering with moonlight
You’re like a peacock dancing
In a garden of flowers
I can’t begin to describe
Your elegance in words
I caress you like the
Shadow that chases you
Yet, you don’t react the slightest, girl
I realize you’re not the girl
Who falls for trickery
Pay heed to this sweet plea
That makes my heart pound
Sweetheart!
I can’t help but fall for you
You know how the heart
Sways to the youth’s beat
Sweetheart!
I can’t help but fall for you
You know how the heart
Sways to the youth’s beat
My eyes are hooked on to your legs
Don’t step on my gaze, show me some mercy
My dreams will guard your eyes like kohl
You set me on fire when
You rub your rosy cheeks
There is a man
called Appal Naidu.
It might be taxes or fees.
You must ask with respect.
You are not meeting him.
You will meet his son.
They are planning to
expand their company.
Ramachandran...
the CEO of this company is getting old.
His son Raj Manohar...
is very slow.
They need money and I want
a part of his company.
His son wants our company.
So, his father is sending him.
Your father is sending you to stop him.
See...
It's easy to say,
"No" to a waiter.
But it's difficult to reject
an influenced person.
So, when you reject
an influential person,
you will earn respect.
Son, it's okay even if
you don't get power.
Be honest. That's enough.
This is the truth.
Bye, dear.
Hello...
I am almost there, ma'am.
Don't worry, your father is
in the hotel right behind us.
Is it the hotel behind us?
Your load is exported to Korea
from our port every month.
That port is not your
father's establishment.
Tell him it belongs
to the government.
But if we shut the gates,
your company will be in dire loss.
There are many ports in this country.
Tell him, Raj.
We will invest in your company.
Welcome us with open arms.
We will be a part
of your company.
Impossible!
Tell him, Raj.
The one in the grey coat?
We can cut down on the diesel cost,
if four people take the same car.
Similarly, you can cut down on holiday
expenses,
if four families travel together.
It was her concept.
It's a great idea.
I believed the same and
invested five crores.
You’ve got a big heart.
She had a turnover of 50
crores in just two years.
She’s got a big brain.
I’m offering 100 crores.
I want the company.
That’s a huge amount.
Why don't you talk?
Say yes, dear.
Say no.
Just say no!
This isn’t a temple where
everyone is welcome.
Besides,
it's a loan when we ask for money.
When we don’t accept the offer.
It's a rejection.
Ma’am will not
sell her company...
Can you speak?
Sir, we floated the company
with affordable travel packages
for the middle-class.
If you buy the company with such a
huge amount, you’ll increase the rates.
It will increase
their travel fare.
So what ma’am is
trying to say is...
This generation has lost
the courage to say "No."
Hey, Das!
They can tussle with us and
still do business in the market?
She’s a girl after all.
We’ll crush you.
That’s a big warning.
Mr. Sudarshan...
I’m not so good
at this pep talk.
It will not match with
my personality either.
But the situation
is demanding it.
Only two people have the
power to create something.
This planet and women.
Why do you want
to mess with them?
We just have to surrender.
If you’re still not convinced,
I have three options.
First...
beat your men and control yourself.
Second, hit you and control you.
Third, predicting that I will
beat you and control yourself.
If you think controlling you is common
in all three options... you’re mistaken.
What’s common is I will
be smacking your men down.
For better or worse...
When someone says no to your
offer, it means...
"No!"
Most importantly,
when a woman says "No", it means...
It's a "No."
Ma’am, we can’t be here after
that speech I just gave.
Let’s get out of here when our
energy levels are high. Come on.
When I saw that guy
in the morning...
it felt like I was looking
at my own reflection.
But when I see my own son
on the computer screen...
He was struggling to say "no."
His weakness felt like my own.
Is this my failure?
Ramu, you were a clerk.
You had to impress
my dad to marry me.
You had to work hard for it.
But my son has nothing to prove.
He was born a Prince.
-Don’t compare him with others.
-I didn’t mean it, Yasu.
I just meant that
guy spoke well.
Suppose we’re on our honeymoon.
How would you feel if I say
some guy hot in front of you?
That’s how I feel when you praise
someone else’s son in front of me.
A mother's love is blind.
That guy caught your attention.
But for me, it was the girl.
She made a lot of progress with
the company in just three years.
If she’s with us,
she can do wonders.
How about we get your
son married to her?
She will bring the
perfect balance.
-Daddy...
-Yes, dear?
Why do I have to wear
a sari for dinner?
Because it’s a dinner
invite from Mr. ARK.
I wouldn’t have cared
if it were someone else.
Don’t be so dumb.
The sari and the bouquet
are to impress them.
Otherwise, a box of
sweets would do it.
Let's go.
In case, they ask
if you can cook.
Lie that you’re
almost good at it.
Why would they ask
me if I could cook?
Is this an alliance?
Just a casual meeting, dear.
Besides, even if they were proposing
marriage... it’s no big deal for them.
Dad!
Dear...
What’s this?
Give it to her if you like her.
Grandpa said it would
be a casual meeting.
You should tell him you won’t meet anyone
else because there your angel is at home.
Hello. Why are you laughing?
Am I not your angel?
I’m Ramachandra.
I’m Anjaneya Prasad.
Even my name suggests
I’m at your service.
-Hey! No! No!
-Dad!
Dear, isn’t it true?
This old man has a knack for
inviting embarrassing guests.
Welcome.
What would you like to have?
We’re blessed to be
sitting next to you.
What more could we ask for?
We’ll eat whatever you serve.
As long as it’s edible.
You have good sense of humor.
You guys aren’t talking much.
Because you are.
My daughter is soft-spoken.
Yeah, right. She doesn’t even
bargain when she goes shopping.
Your son is soft-spoken as well.
He expressed it with a box.
My dear, you’re so lucky!
Fortune is calling.
My miserable days are over.
It feels like the Lords of
Wealth are paying me a visit.
What are you looking at? Get up!
Give it a second thought.
This whole time,
you were worried about him being slow.
Now you’re worried
that he’s going fast.
Dad!
What are you waiting for?
Let’s get them engaged.
Why are you crying?
Tears of joy.
What are you doing here?
Ma’am called me...
I thought she had some work...
You don't have any work here.
Go!
Well...
I bought that ring so that
he will marry my daughter.
He’s doing it.
You turned this lunch
into an engagement.
My daughter had a lot of
expectations on her wedding.
Then let’s make sure
we don’t fall short.
My daughter will commit
suicide if she can’t marry him.
She aspired to become a
collector when she was a kid.
Did that happen?
She will not do
everything she says.
Don’t worry.
Come on.
This is all your fault.
What did I do?
Because you hit Sudarshanam’s men
and Mr. Ramachandra noticed you.
Because he noticed you,
he spoke to my father.
Because he spoke to my
father, I had to get engaged.
Did Sudarshanam get
scared and back off?
He called us to the police
station for a meeting.
-Don't worry, ma'am.
-Hey...
-Sit.
-But, ma'am.
No, you are angry.
Is she your wife?
No way.
She's my boss.
But her body language
says something else.
She’s scolding you with
so much confidence.
You can judge by body language?
My foot!
She already got
engaged yesterday.
I don't think so.
It'll work out soon.
What's going to happen?
You are not Ramachandra's son.
She's very practical.
Reddy influenced him.
Hey, stop it... stop it.
It will work out, trust me.
-What are you saying?
-Really?
-What's the issue?
-Sir, I gave her five crores.
We asked for our money
and he got physical.
He didn't just ask for money.
He wants the whole company.
He was being insensitive to girls.
That is when I hit him, sir.
-Did he cuss women?
-Yes, sir.
Then you have to
file a case on him.
Hey... call the writer.
He’s not some fighter that
you’d call the writer.
Look at him.
Look at my bodyguard.
-How can we believe this guy hit him?
-You have a point.
That’s a lie, sir. I hit him.
I’ll hit him again if I have to.
-Can you notice any difference?
-What difference?
He was standing until now,
but now he is sitting there.
Maybe he is tired of
standing, so he sat down.
I hit him and he fell there.
Give me a break.
I hit him when you bent down.
He was in the air when you stood up.
He was sitting by
the time you saw him.
Dear...
Why don't you take
him to a good doctor?
What’s wrong? What happened?
It's a stylish fight scene, sir.
Things like these don’t happen often.
All of you together
made it a big lie.
I'm hurt.
You are hurt?
-What's your problem?
-I just hit him again, sir.
But I didn't see it.
-Call him back. I can hit him again.
-That's wrong.
You can’t say such things
to the police.
You don’t believe me when I say I hit him.
You don’t look when I hit him.
You don’t agree when
offer to hit him again.
You’re impossible, sir.
Dear...
Why do you want
to get locked up?
-You have a bright future.
-I know, sir.
Don't interrupt me while I talk!
I'll kill you!
-Dear, what does he do for you?
-Annoy me.
So, nobody believes I hit him.
Hey! This is your final chance.
I’ll ask her.
Whatever she says is final.
-You should stand by that.
-Yes.
Did he beat that guy?
Ma’am, you are also lying.
Why are you so keen
on getting arrested?
But I had to tell the truth.
I don’t want the engagement.
Did I say it out?
-We can’t tell the truth all the time.
-Exactly.
Nothing will go wrong if
you tell the truth, ma’am.
You should do the
same with your dad.
I told him.
He said he’ll commit suicide.
Then tell Raj’s father.
Mr. Ramachandra?
Ma’am… listen to me, please.
Try telling
Mr. Ramachandra once.
-Trust me and tell the truth.
-Okay, I will.
Give me that.
Telling the truth solves
all problems, ma’am.
It really feels light.
Because I took the bag from you?
No, you idiot!
I meant I feel lighter.
I feel lighter!
Enough!
It’s obvious to be scared
when you hit someone suddenly.
He’s an idiot, man.
Why do you care if he’s scared?
-I don’t mean him. I’m scared! Me!
-You’re scared. I get it.
I have full clarity now.
Are you hurt?
Yes, but it feels good, ma’am.
You are beating me.
Don’t call me ma’am.
It'll take time, ma'am.
Call me Amulya.
I know your name, ma'am.
It'll take time, ma'am.
It'll take lot of time.
Did she fall for you?
I already told you.
Get out!
Who can be a better match to me?
Why didn’t I realize this before, Ammu?
Love is like chewing gum
It sticks with you
And doesn’t let go
People have said this before
But let me say it again
I can’t hold it in
You can’t restrain from love
You are everything
I’ve been looking for
You became a part of me
Before I knew it
Hey, pretty doll
You’ve surrounded my thoughts
You’ve held my hand in togetherness
Hey, pretty doll
You’ve surrounded my thoughts
You’ve held my hand in togetherness
I might have been quiet
like an audience in a theater
But there are drums
Playing in my heart
I might have just
Had a brain freeze
This isn’t the Kings’ times,
No chariot or horses
I fight a battle against myself
In front of the mirror
You put forward your hands filled
With bangles and come close
You caress my cheeks and
Make me feel like a King
I asked for pitter-patter raindrops
You’ve given me a cyclone
I asked for a little jasmine
You showered me with flowers
Hey, pretty doll
You’ve surrounded my thoughts
You’ve held my hand in togetherness
You’ve made me an eternal part of you
You’ve given me a special place
In your heart
Who can be a better match to me?
Why didn’t I realize this before, Ammu?
Love is like chewing gum
It sticks with you
And doesn’t let go
People have said this before
But let me say it again
I can’t hold it in
You can’t restrain from love
He’ll be seeing you now.
I’m Appala Naidu.
I control everything
in the port.
I got my son into college so that
he has a different lifestyle.
I sent him to you with money
because your company needed it.
My son made it clear that
we don’t need your money.
Your son might listen
to whatever you say.
But I'll give my son
whatever her asks for.
If you try to stop it.
People from Kolkata
love to eat fish brains.
People from Andhra
love its tail.
But the fish loves to live.
To do so, it must stay
farther away from the net.
Once it falls into the
net, there’s no going back.
Let’s tell him later… not now.
We've have come very far.
Let's tell the truth.
Where is he?
Maybe he is in the restroom.
-Sit down.
-It’s okay.
-Shall I call the ambulance?
-No… call the car driver.
Hey! Hey!
Where’s the staircase?
What happened?
-Any chances of making it?
-Only God can save him now.
God doesn’t exist anymore.
Move... let him breathe.
-Shall I call his family?
-Not now... Later.
Hey!
-That’s our car.
-We stabbed him.
Let it go.
-You said he had no chance.
-You said God didn’t exist.
I'll inform his family.
Calm down, ma’am.
One moment.
Do you know him?
-What…
-What happened?
Someone...
He met with a small accident.
Don’t worry. He’s fine.
Is he your father?
My father?
Sadly, no.
No.
He's my father.
He's there.
Tell me.
That’s not your father.
Your father is...
Ra... Ra... Rama...
It doesn’t change the
fact that he’s my father.
You need to relax.
Please sit, sir.
I’ll check if ma'am is here.
He’s... he’s not your father.
He’s not your father.
I don’t think you’re feeling well.
Let me call the doctor.
Wait a minute... stop talking.
He’s... not your father.
He’s Valmiki.
You know my father?
Valmiki is not your father.
Ramachandra... is your father.
What do you mean?
I don’t get it.
Yes...
Ramachandra is your father.
I switched you.
You didn’t move
when you were born.
Before I could tell
the doctor about it...
Your... your name?
You were born as Raj.
You are the real Raj.
I picked you up from
the rich side...
and put you into a poor family.
That guilt is killing me.
Only God and I know that.
I have to tell this to
your father before I die.
I should only tell him.
Call him...
Raj... call your father.
Call him!
Get Ramachandra here.
Call him.
Raj... Raj... call your father.
Get Ramachandra.
Call him.
He's inside.
What is the patient doing here?
Sister, what are you doing?
You’re supposed to be alert.
What is this patient doing here?
-Is Dr. Bhaskar Reddy available?
-Yes, sir.
Let’s shift her
to critical care.
-My daughter…
-On the way, sir.
I spoke with the doctors.
His heart is totally fine.
Just some blood loss.
He should recover soon.
No issues so far...
I have it all sorted.
I don’t think so, Kasi.
Hello, ma’am.
-Where’s father?
-He’s sitting in the back.
-Call him.
-Okay, ma’am.
Who is he?
So, it’s you brother-in-law
was bragging about.
He saved uncle.
He was also at the
hotel last time.
I didn’t notice.
Ask him to wait downstairs.
I’ll talk to him later.
Father,
DCP wants to talk to you.
Come dear.
Let’s go.
This is how the
rich people are...
They never fail to
remind us our place.
We can never be one of them.
I’ve been working with
them for 25 years.
But they never let me in.
We should get used to this.
That’s the way it is.
We’re strangers.
We must behave like strangers.
You know what they say.
A King’s Palace hosts
the prosperous alone.
Just because he’s
gotten close to us...
We shouldn’t think like that.
She’s no more.
Poor lady.
Take her away.
Do you know her?
Must be an orphan.
You know I am very sensitive.
I can’t take it.
She must’ve done
something bad.
She had a remorseful death.
God’s watching over all of us.
You have something to say?
Hey! How dare you!
I’m annoyed listening to
your lies from childhood.
But you never stop it.
Actually,
why don’t you take a break?
Hey!
Sit properly...
you are leaning on me.
As soon as you do
something good...
you can’t resist
doing something bad.
You can ask me why I hit you.
Why are you beating
around the bush?
You just hit your dad and you’re
passing statements about it?
We’re in the middle of the road.
Do you have something to say?
You’re not the real father.
That is why I hit you.
I’m not your father?
How do you think
you were born then?
Did you pop out of thin air?
No, I didn’t.
You got me down.
That nurse was in
coma for 25 years.
How can you believe
whatever she mumbles?
I don’t remember mentioning
anything about a nurse.
Tell me.
Is Ramachandra my father?
Yes or no?
You couldn’t shut up ever since I was
born. Now speak up!
Tell me!
I...
I just wanted my
son to be happy.
I get that part.
But why did you torture me?
You are jealous of my father.
He started along with you and
became a millionaire in no time.
You couldn’t take it.
But there’s nothing
you can do to him.
So, you picture Ramachandra in me.
Exactly why you’ve been
troubling me for 25 years.
You drove me crazy.
What have I done to you?
Drink it...
You look like you’re going to die.
Will you reveal everything and
expose me in front of everyone?
Will you ruin my son’s life?
I'm begging you.
Please don’t tell anyone.
If I reveal the truth...
they will abandon
your son right away.
His mother will
become his madam.
His father will become his boss.
A clerk like you will
be his real father.
He will commit suicide
out of depression and die.
I considered all this and
chose to be silent back there.
Besides, it’s my mother who’s
going to weep if I expose you.
I can’t call her auntie after she
nurtured me for all these years.
I can’t call her my mom
just for the sake of wealth.
I don’t want your wealth or their stature.
You only keep it. I don’t need it.
You don’t want any of it.
What will you get from
knowing the truth?
The freedom of knowing that
I don’t have to impress you.
Ever since I was a kid,
I’ve been looking for ways to impress you.
Now I realized you’re not
going to like me after all.
I’ve found my answer.
I always get irritated
when I see you.
But for the first time,
I feel sorry for you.
Because...
you can’t claim him as your son.
I won’t accept you as my father.
Few lives don’t get any better.
My vehicle has insurance.
I'm sure he won’t tell anyone.
Oh God!
Mother...
Aren’t you feeling well?
Sister told me you
didn't eat anything.
I’ve been having
temperature since evening.
Your boiling.
Wait.
I’ll get you some medicine.
No.
You can’t do this.
Get her some medicines.
No.
I just want my
kids to comfort me.
I will get better.
I want to meet your son.
I'll give him a
hug and thank him.
Get him once.
I’m the doctor that
treated your son-in-law.
She’s the nurse
that assisted me.
You need to hug the
both of us and thank us.
How could you think someone
else is more important?
-Who is he?
-Hey!
Come with me for a moment.
We shouldn’t upset
doctors and drivers.
The syringes and steering
wheels are in their control.
Let’s get out of here.
What’s the matter, Dad?
You were supposed to
be here yesterday.
But no one told me about it.
A son is supposed to check
on his father and mother.
And also, on what’s going
on around the house.
Nobody will tell you.
I can’t believe you brought
a bouquet like some stranger.
How much is the bill?
Change the figure. Ten lakhs.
The figure for one lakh
twenty thousand would be one lakh.
Not ten lakhs.
You’re not Subrahmanyam.
-No.
-What’s up, sir?
He knows nothing
about figures.
Explain it to him.
If we charge the medicines at ten lakhs...
This bill is going to top Jayalalitha’s.
Luckily, she didn’t have
a brother like him.
Otherwise, her bill would
have crossed the state budget.
Her husband is in a
critical condition.
And yet,
she hasn’t shed a single tear.
She didn’t sob for him like we did.
Really?
Yeah!
What?
They are of a different class.
Different class?
Are you crazy?
The husband and the wife don’t
have a proper conversation.
His son gets him a bouquet
like he’s a stranger.
Don’t even get me started
on his brother-in-law.
He’s looting all their money
in the name of hospital bills.
Why do we care about them?
I don’t get it.
How come the father and the son
are having a conversation
without turning it into a fight?
It’s nothing.
I was telling him that
house is like a temple.
And the couple is like
Lord Shiva and Parvathi.
That's it.
You call that a temple?
Who are you then?
The priest’s sidekick?
Not a single member in
that family has values.
If they keep this going...
my father will die.
Stop bragging that
he is your father.
I’m your father.
If you ever say that again,
I’ll kill your mom and kill myself next.
I swear on God!
Why are you getting
my mom into this?
Because you wouldn’t
care if I died alone.
You have something to say now?
I want to go to that house.
What happened?
-Dad choked.
-Give him some water.
I’m at it.
Drink.
Drink it.
You’ve been checking on your
son since the last 25 years.
Now it’s my turn
to check on my dad.
Hey...
You can check on your Prince.
But I can’t check on my King?
Even if you’re in the same
room with Ramachandra...
he’s going to take you in right away.
You’re his blood after all.
That is what kept me from
taking you to that house.
Besides, would you stay
away once you got in?
You’re like a chewing
gum stuck on the shoe.
I’ll never let you go there.
Who can get me in other than you?
You’re going to take me there.
-Me?
-Yeah. Tomorrow.
You better lose the
T-shirts for a while, sir.
Shirts will be comfortable.
-Why?
-Not again!
My son-in-law is not too
old to wear a T-shirt.
Hey! What does a T-shirt
have to do with it?
Wearing a dhoti doesn’t
make you any better.
Calm down, doctor.
Get it?
But you don’t understand.
You can wear shorts if you want.
Your calves will get some fresh air.
What about you?
What?
-Not again.
-Hang on.
He needs pleasant people around.
Especially people unlike us.
That guy who brought
him to the hospital.
Why don’t you just
call the same guy?
Come here!
See?
Your son-in-law’s BP is normal
as soon as I mentioned that guy.
Look.
How is his presence going
to help medically, doctor?
You will see for yourself.
In the movies, a child gets better
when his mom or dad visits him.
You believe in that stuff.
But you don’t believe in an
overqualified doctor like me.
You question my credibility.
But you didn’t want
him here last time.
Answer him.
I will.
Didn’t you say that?
I did, sir.
But people change.
Give me a chance, will you?
Even doctors and
drivers have kids.
The doctor’s BP might
rise from all the yelling.
Go get him.
He’ll be at work now.
Ask him to take permission
for a few hours.
-It’s not a government office.
-Ask him to take the rest of the day off.
What reason would he give?
Just ask him to quit the job.
Good riddance!
-That’s his bread and butter, doctor.
-Send him to my house.
I’ll feed him bread and butter.
-It’s no big deal. Let’s hire him.
-Yes!
You’re always giving some excuse
whenever I want to see him.
Don’t you want him here?
-What’s your problem?
-I don’t have any problem.
-Then call him.
Battery is low. I will...
-Give me his number. I’ll call him.
-I will only call him.
Hello...
Why are you stepping out?
Because the signals
are better there.
Make the call quickly and
my life will be better.
You must be lucky.
Yesterday you told me.
Today they are only inviting you.
Every fool has his day.
Today is your day.
Just because they invited you,
doesn’t mean I’ll let you come.
I’ll give them some lame
excuse to keep you away.
The doctor will call me
as soon as you hang up.
How do you know there’s
a doctor inside?
Where are you?
Stop limping and look up.
Hey! What’s with the doctor?
He hated you last time.
But now, he’s acting like
some die-hard fan of yours.
It’s an obvious reaction for
someone who had his son kidnapped.
You kidnapped his son?
It's him.
This fatso?
Is he coming?
Yes, sir.
This doctor is killing me.
Please come.
In a far-off city named Vaikunthapuram
Further away from
The humongous palace
At the shore of a sea filled with nectar
There was a dais shining like the moon
Lord Vishnu was seated with Goddess Laxmi
On a throne adorned with black lotuses
Being the holy savior, he rushes to
The rescue of the helpless Gajendra
Here sets foot a new relationship
In the abode of Vaikunthapuram
Here comes the epitome of joy
To a place weeping with sadness
Here forms a new acquaintance
In the abode of Vaikunthapuram
Here he brings happiness to
People flooding with tears
Here holds an umbrella
The sky for the cloud arriving
Here sighs with relief the world
For he will be a pillar of support
Here welcomes the ravishing sun
As the holy vermilion
In the abode of Vaikunthapuram...
Hey! Why did you give her money?
My son.
And my son?
He’s at the tea shop.
I’ll be there in a second.
-I didn’t pay for the tea.
-I will.
He has my headphones.
I’ll get you new headphones.
You guys are criminals
for kidnapping kids.
Your father has been
hiding you like a bride.
I never got to take
a good look at you.
Come forward.
He’s good.
You’re a tough man.
You didn’t just carry my
son-in-law the other day.
You carried the prestige of this
house, ARK Company and our hopes.
You work for my
granddaughter, right?
Yes, sir.
-Is she paying you well?
-Yes, sir.
How much?
I was promised 25 thousand… I get 20
thousand after all the exclusions.
I’ll pay you 50 thousand.
Come work for me.
Sir! He’ll be spoiled if you
promise him so much money.
What are you talking?
You’ll be spoiling him
if you gave him money.
But we will be encouraging him.
No, sir...
-Work for me.
-Sure, sir.
Choose any room you like and
find a desk and a computer.
-But what would I do?
-Exactly my question.
He will watch pictures
of girls on the Internet.
We can think about that later.
I have a lot of people to
meet and loads of work to do.
Time for you to leave.
Go!
Idiot.
You need to be straightforward
in everything you do.
I hate people who lie.
What?
You just proved that you could
insist on something you don’t do.
You’re an inspiration
to a set of people, sir.
I'm an inspiration?
Hey, ma’am! How are you doing?
Didn’t you recognize me?
Come. Sit.
I was at the hotel for
madam’s engagement, remember?
Never mind, ma’am.
I know you don’t remember me.
I don’t mind.
Hero Chiranjeevi
waves at his fans.
It doesn’t mean he knows
all their names.
It's the same for you.
You’re like a star.
And I’m like your biggest fan.
See?
Even I have a good following.
Of course.
To be honest... you might look
above average but you’re super sexy.
Yes.
Don’t hit your fans.
Bro, come here.
Tell me, bro.
Just look at her…
she’s superhot.
I can't make those comments.
Tell me what this is about.
Let me know who her
close relatives are here.
I want to be friends with them.
-Not possible.
-Why?
I’m her uncle.
Sorry, sir.
Going by your clothes,
I thought you were the maid.
What do you mean?
You want me to suit
up at home as well?
How do you like the house?
It’s wonderful, sir.
But I don’t like that fact that he was
attacked despite having all of you around.
Why didn’t you file
a police complaint?
We did, man.
-We did file a complaint.
-You can be informal with me.
You’re elder to me.
The guy we’re dealing with
is quite powerful as well.
We don’t have enough
evidence to support the case.
So, the police are
afraid to arrest him.
Why is that stopping us?
We'll go and talk to him.
-Shall we?
-Yeah!
Who are you?
This is too much, Paidithalli.
You want shares in his company. You want
to be the director of his company.
You also want his position
if you can have it.
But you don’t know him.
Who let you in?
It was very hard to come here...
We took flight until Rajahmundry
and in a car until Kakinada.
After reaching this place…
it was uncomfortable.
Sir, you can’t go in.
Let’s go. Start the vehicle.
No, sir. We traveled so far.
That hand print…
Who pushed him?
My nephew visited your office and you
asked him to get out in a video call.
But you expect grand
welcome from us?
Impossible!
-My load is in there.
-So what?
I am giving you 25 to 30
crores business every year.
So what?
Hey! I need to go inside.
Don’t you get it, old man?
Lift the load. Come on.
Who pushed him?
Who the hell do you think you
are, barging into our port?
Who pushed him?
Who raised his hand on him?
Was it you?
You pushed him?
-Tell me.
-No…
I didn’t push him.
Did you push him?
Tell me!
How dare you guys push him!
Pick up the stuff
that old man dropped.
Cardamom tea, sir.
Especially for you.
Towel sprayed with cologne, sir.
It will cool you down.
Who was it?
Who pushed him?
You’ve been asking the
same question since you came.
You seriously don’t think a bunch
of people pushed him, do you?
Only one guy pushed him
and you hit him long back.
He’s there.
Where’s your boss?
We need to yell his name out and call him.
If you spare us the time that is.
It can’t get any
clearer than this.
He is trying to say that...
your father stabbed
his son-in-law.
But there was no evidence.
Case is hanging by a weak link now.
I came and hit you guys.
And there’s no evidence here as well.
This case will also be weak.
Let’s not play this
game of tit for tat.
Let’s sit down and talk it out.
Sir strongly feels we
shouldn’t resort to violence.
What do you think?
What are you looking at? Get up!
You were quick on your feet a while ago.
Now you’re looking sloppy.
We’ll be late for our flight. Let’s go.
Brother, you have anything else to ask?
This is sad!
Our Prince won't talk...
This Prince has nothing to say.
Both of you are unique.
What is that?
Isn’t this boat
supposed to be on water?
-It’s a car, man.
-I know that.
I was wondering
what's the name.
Sounds like a
Rajamouli film title.
Wow! Amazing contrast, boss!
The car’s classy look doesn’t
go with your appeal at all.
Let’s take a selfie.
Nice umbrella.
I’ve seen people use it
when it’s sunny or raining.
But this is the first time,
I saw someone use it to stab.
I can’t stab
artistically like you.
I’m rough like that.
You just got down the car.
I just got into my character.
Don’t be shy.
I’ll see you around.
Come.
We’ll be late for our flight.
But I have to admit, boss.
It’s a great car.
Hey, wait!
He warned you in our port.
I'll kill him.
They will give us their
company shares very soon.
Where will they go?
Go.
Don’t ask silly questions like
where and how he got stabbed.
They’re not like us.
They belong to the elite.
You’re wearing a cute
skirt after so long.
Dear…
Who is he?
Then why is he
getting all touchy?
You didn’t tell him?
What does she have to tell me?
Your daughter is not so
interested in the groom.
So?
So, we took things
a little too far.
Oh, that was shocking.
Don’t tell them anything now.
That is why we didn't tell
you, Dad.
Why is he calling me "Dad"?
Ammu’s dad is my dad.
Right, Dad?
Ammu! Come fast!
-For now?
-If possible, forever.
Come on!
How are you?
-This is Jubilee Hills Road no. 36, right?
-Yes, sir.
-What are you doing here then?
-I work here.
What’s the job?
They still didn't give
me any designation.
For now, I’m browsing pictures
of girls on the internet.
What brings you here?
I’m here to meet
Mr. Ramachandra.
Whatever it is,
you can tell me, sir.
I can’t discuss it with a kid.
Commissioner wanted me to ask if
Mr. Ramachandra needs security.
He doesn’t need security
while I’m around, sir.
Listen… I’m like a one-man army.
Who the hell are you to make
decisions about his security?
Come closer.
What?
Well...
I am Mr. Ramachandra’s real son.
It’s true, sir.
I’m Mr. Ramachandra’s son.
I swear on you!
What about him?
They’ve been assuming he’s
their son for 25 years.
For 25 years?
-When did you find out?
-Recently.
-Who told you?
-A nurse told me.
Nurse and that guy
hiding behind the pillar…
They replaced him with me,
putting me into a middle-class family.
And replaced me with him,
making him heir to a rich family.
-Who told you?
-No, Nurse told me.
-When did she tell you?
-Recently.
-Why didn’t she tell you 25 years ago?
-Because she was in a coma.
-Why did she tell you now?
-Because she came out of the coma.
-Did she tell you about it?
-Why would she tell everyone in the world?
She should have told
Mr. Ramachandra.
-She was about to tell him.
-Then why didn’t she tell him?
Because she died before
she could tell him.
Do you want some tea?
No... I need whiskey.
I'll drink in the evening
after my working hours.
Okay.
Bantu, my dear.
Does anyone else know
about this apart from you?
No one knows, sir.
I won’t tell anyone either.
I’ll sacrifice.
If you’re so sacrificing,
why did you come to this house?
Who else will look after my
house, sir?
Reddy will kill me.
I need to go to the office urgently.
I’ll see you in the evening.
What is she doing here?
His fiancé.
Why is she kissing you then?
Because we are in love.
-Does he know?
-Come on, sir!
Why would he marry
her if he knew about it?
Does Ramachandra
know this at least?
We were going to tell him and
something terrible happened.
Naughty boy!
Who is she?
His nephew.
-Why is she spanking you?
-I don't know.
She’s been flirting with me
ever since I joined here.
Now she is spanking me.
Nice!
You flirt with all the
girls in this house.
And he doesn't care about it.
I can’t see this anymore.
I’ll leave.
Sir, do you run a background check
on the employees you are hiring?
We do check.
Then why did you hire him?
What are you talking about?
If there’s anyone in this house with
the common sense and intelligence I do…
It’s him.
Very nice!
Oh, man! I’m done with you.
Oh, God!
How did it go, sir?
It was horrifying.
We assume all rich
people are intelligent.
But they’re just lucky.
After you joined here,
we didn't speak properly.
They said you went out.
I was talking to the SP, sir.
It’s about the attack.
He was asking if you need security.
We close our doors when
there is heavy breeze.
But what can we do if
the storm is in our home.
We have to accept it.
When we are in tough situations,
we look to our
family for strength.
But when that family
is your weakness...
who do you look to?
Bantu,
even God needs an offering.
Even a King needs protection.
I don't want to tell him
my problems and worry him.
My son won’t understand
even if I told him.
There’s no point
in telling them.
The greatest battles are
fought with the closest people.
What did my son-in-law say?
He said a lot.
Is he upset about the
differences with my daughter?
Of course, he would be.
It’s been seven years since
they had a proper conversation.
Did he tell you anything else?
He didn’t tell me anything, sir.
-But you just did.
-Oh no!
You can’t keep a secret, right?
What?
I won’t live for another
100 years to be patient.
I need to know
everything immediately.
-Okay.
-So, what did he say?
-He said something about his son.
-Is he feeling bad?
He is a strange guy.
Sit, sit.
No one knows what’s
in his heart.
I want to see him burst out in
anger, I’ll die a happy man.
I'll help you!
You don’t need to die for it.
You don't go to office.
You are sitting
outside and smoking.
They are very innocent.
This is wrong.
I am the owner! My wish!
-Get out! Get out!
-Rascal!
He’s got something, man.
Grandpa is giving him
way too much lenience.
Ramachandra treats him
like a family member.
We should be friends with him.
Why do you want
to mess things up?
One and a half lakh
expenditure every day?
We’re discussing accounts here
and why are you hitting them?
Because they hit me.
-Why did they hit you?
-Because they stole one lakh.
Why did they hit you only?
Because they gave me share.
Give me that stick.
For what?
Because I have to hit them.
Uncle! Uncle! No!
You don’t worry.
I’ll go get sister.
What’s going on, Sita?
What happened?
Stop running and let him hit you...
he will be satisfied.
Yasu, uncle is beating
me just because he said.
What’s wrong, Dad?
Why are you hitting him?
After finding out how much
money he’s looting every day…
what did you expect from me?
Who told you?
He told me.
How do you know if it's true?
He will tell me
only if it’s true.
Oh, really?
You speak the truth, right?
Tell me.
Why will he loot our money?
We are paying him ten
lakhs every month.
He bets a million
rupees on a poker table.
He’s a big player.
Dad, you gamble?
Only on the weekends.
That’s it. Yeah.
He talks to Priya
on the weekdays.
-Who’s Priya?
-How would I know?
Not everything you say is true.
You have a message from Priya in
the mobile you threw on the floor.
It reads, "Call me."
What’s the big deal?
She just asked me to call back.
-There is no controversy here.
-Actually, she called you baby in the end.
She also sent a heart emoticon.
In red.
Don’t look, sir.
Her pictures are on it.
Really?
Why are you hitting me
when it’s his fault?
Where were you when
all this was happening?
What do you expect me to do?
Find a girl for myself?
Hey! When will you women change?
You hit your brothers just because
you can't slap your husbands.
They’re outdated.
They will never change.
Why is he running away if
Bantu wasn’t telling the truth?
Alright then. I’ll hear you out.
Tell about me.
Isn’t that too
much for the day?
You come with me.
Father!
You tell me.
You don’t get along
with your husband.
Bantu! Come with me.
Dad!
How do you know?
You shut your room door
the first time I was here.
I knew it right away.
Wife and husband go
through a lot of stuff.
They will shut and open
doors as they please.
If a newlywed couple
closes the door…
it means they have something
personal to talk about.
But if they still shut
the door after 25 years…
It means they don’t want the world
to know they’re not on talking terms.
He comes home at six o'clock,
no matter how busy he is.
So, he’s implying that his life
revolves around family and work only.
And when a man is trying so
hard, it means that…
he did something
wrong in the past.
What is it?
She was his secretary
seven years ago.
She resigned only
after a month’s duty.
Back then…
The sad part is everyone
knew about this.
But everyone pretends
like it’s nothing.
Including your father.
Do you think telling the
truth makes you great?
When kids don't eat food...
their mother will tell
them a scary story.
Is that wrong on her part?
Try and love someone.
You will know what
a lie is worth.
That mother also tells her grown up kid
that he’ll fall sick if he doesn’t eat.
She won't lie to him.
You’ll know what a lie is worth
when you love someone. I get it.
But you’ll know how strong your love
is, only when you tell the truth.
It might be tough.
But a relationship built on
truth stays solid as a rock, sir.
It’s five o'clock.
Time for me to go off duty.
Does this mark the end of this episode?
Or is it going to be continued tomorrow?
Go!
She is not educated like you...
Or beautiful like you.
Or superior to you in any way.
Maybe that is why I liked her...
because of my
inferiority complex.
Is it my fault that
I tried to be my best?
Is that why you are hurting me?
Have I ever compared
myself to her?
But, dear...
don’t I deserve a sorry?
Earlier, you would try to prove that
you are the perfect match for me.
Now you are just trying to prove
you’re not doing anything wrong.
Why, Ramu?
Why?
Why do you have to
prove anything to me?
Be yourself.
Just be your true self.
There’s nothing I’d want more.
Hey!
I was scared, Yasu...
to look into your
eyes and talk to you.
I was scared...
for the things I've done.
How do I make it up to you?
Why isn’t my daughter reacting?
Don’t ruin the moment
with your curiosity.
Give them some time.
They are hugging each other.
Then close your eyes
and let me have my meal.
Shall I tell you
something mind blowing?
ARK brought Ramachandra
into this house.
He made him the clerk
and soon the CEO.
Finally made him his son-in-law,
only for him to torture us ever since.
He brought home
this new guy now.
And this guy has only
doubled the torture.
That old man brings someone home and
that guy gets us into trouble every time.
What if we brought someone home?
That guy will be
on our side then.
We can loot a huge
sum of amount.
But who do we call?
Should we call Sudarshan?
She can handle him easily.
He's a pilot... another
guy planned this meeting.
He is Paidithalli.
He alone can handle
all of them easily.
Mr. Ramachandra already said
we don’t want this deal, right?
His son was looking hesitant.
So, he had to do it
out of courtesy.
But he didn’t completely
want to reject the deal.
So, I called him
back to discuss it.
Let’s see what
they’ve got to offer.
Besides,
if he goes on rejecting everyone…
You know...
Did they send you to say "No"?
No matter what,
I will make sure they say "Yes."
She can’t do it alone.
I have to go.
You sit down.
-Yasu, I have to go.
-I don’t care.
You are important to me.
Okay? Sit down.
Wives often push their husbands
to earn more, son-in-law.
A wife who asks her husband
to relax is a rare sight.
I know who can deal with them.
Good sign! Hold this, sister.
I didn't zip up.
Put it on me.
Suit looks good.
Hey! Hey! Where are you going?
Why are you all decked up?
Relax!
I got it.
We have made all the
arrangements to buy shares.
Who are you?
The savior is here
He brought showers to the barren land
The savior does what he does best
He has given us the hope of new beginnings
The savior is here
He brought showers to the barren land
He’s at the port, the board
meeting and basically everywhere.
Madam is like your
sir’s speaker.
Is he like her mic?
This is way too many people for a meeting.
I want to hear from only one of you.
Why don't you stay?
This heart belongs to you
Why don't you hug me tight?
Hold me closer to your heart
Is he playing the song for my nephew? Or
is he making the most of this situation?
I wonder if the word "beauty"
Was coined after you
I'm too shy to ask you for a hug
Why don't you stay?
Now that she has left…
we’ll have to see what he can do.
I will show you
what I’m made of.
I'll make you go crazy
I'll make you cheer
for every moment
I'll make you go crazy
I'll make you cheer for every moment
It’s time for you to play
a Pawan Kalyan track.
Situation doesn’t demand
it, Mr. Sitaram.
His songs don’t need a situation.
We’re demanding it, right?
Hey!
Welcome to Vividha
Bharathi’s special telecast.
Here's a request of Sitaram,
brother-in-law of Kasiram from Kakinada.
A song from
"Gabbar Singh."
What are you guys looking at me for?
Start playing the drums
That's right!
Hey, girl... a life without you is
Like a spinning top without a thread
Like a cracker slipped into water
What was that?
Get down. Idiot!
Is this a board room or a ball room?
Hey!
Do you know who signed that?
Do you know him? Tell me!
Your song?
It’s you? You?
Mine?
It's mine.
We covered the megastar’s song as well.
His timing is amazing.
When will they change?
Why is everyone running
away when he hit one person?
Shall we go?
I feel something is
missing, Bantu.
Incomplete?
But I’ve played such a
versatile compilation.
Did you miss the dialogue?
Father is unwell.
Mother can’t go to work.
Grandpa is getting older...
Grandson is young.
Just because you have
cars and the roads are empty...
don’t come here
whenever you want.
They have a brother.
He will stand in your way.
What?
A whistle isn’t enough.
We need blasting background music.
Slow motion… things flying in the air…
we need lot of special effects to it.
I’ll plan it... let's go.
What happened?
Son-in-law,
Bantu hit this one out of the park.
Dear,
I’m throwing a party tonight.
And I’m going to drink.
Brother, stop it.
Do you have any desi music
instead of this English music?
Wow! That sounds great.
Whom do we talk about?
Reddy? His life is boring.
Sekhar? No way.
I'll tell about myself.
Bantu was a well-known dude in his area
He had a bunch of guys
Follow him everywhere
They got on their bikes
One night for alcohol
They crashed every store for alcohol
There she was,
Shining like a beer in silk a sari
Tempting me like a packet of hot biryani
Standing on the terrace,
She was like the moon
Her beauty got me high,
Without having to booze
While she was hopping
Around like a deer
Her earring fell
And it stuck my heart
Oh, boy! She blew my mind
Oh, boy! She blew my heart
Every time I eat betel leaf,
I think of your scent
Your red blushing cheeks
Take over my mind
Every time I wear a floral shirt,
You bloom like a button
You barge into my heart
And create chaos inside
When the bulb in front of my house
flickers
It seems like you’re winking at me
Naughtily
When my drapes are stuck in the door hinge
It seems like you’re pulling them
And it gives me goosebumps
Like a snake swaying to
The snake charmer’s tune
I follow your track as
Your anklets begin to clink
You go around like you don’t care, sweetie
You hide and peep from a corner
Oh boy! She blew my mind
Oh boy! She blew my heart
This house provided us a living.
It fed us through
all these years.
And when they welcomed you
to this house with open arms…
what did you do?
You got into a
brawl with a rowdy.
You kidnapped a little kid.
You blackmailed a millionaire.
You also started flirting with
their future daughter-in-law.
Someone like you don’t
deserve a place in any house.
Get out.
Stop calling me Valmiki.
Haven’t I taught you better?
I’m your dad! So, call me that.
Get out.
You must be tired of telling the
truth ever since you were a kid.
Take a break.
When you were born, it only took me
25 minutes to bring you downstairs.
But it took you 25 years
to climb back to the top.
This time I am pushing you.
There’s no way you can climb back up.
Impossible!
Yes, ma’am… I am coming.
VAIKUNTHAPURAM.
Thank God. It’s over.
Why are you sad, Bantu?
This is what we’ve been
trying to tell them.
Even I’ve been trying
to tell you something.
Did you tell your real
parents the truth?
I’ll never tell them.
Then there is no point
in going to that house.
I don't get it.
Did I leave all my problems?
It feels like I left a blank
answer sheet in the examination hall.
Those papers state that half of
your company's share belongs to me.
I want you both to
sign on the papers
and send them to my
farmhouse with your son.
If you don’t, I’ll send your
niece’s dead body in an hour.
If you don’t seek the police,
it will just be a kidnap.
But if you do...
it will end up being a murder.
Get it?
Brother-in-law…
Get up.
Brother-in-law...
It was thrilling to loot someone’s
money without their notice.
But I didn’t know it’d be so burdening
if they gave up the money willingly.
I can’t carry it around.
I don’t know how to repay you.
I can’t believe you gave up
your wealth for my daughter.
She grew up right in
front of my eyes, Kasi.
Isn’t she my daughter as well?
Calm down, Kasi.
Raj… Raj… I don’t
want you to go.
Your family has already
done a lot for us.
I can’t forgive myself if
anything happened to you.
-I will only go… give it to me.
-Uncle, he asked me to get it.
Come on. Give me the money.
It’s okay. I will convince them.
He’s right, sir.
Let him fight for his daughter.
You can’t do it.
Come here.
Sir, tell him.
Raj is innocent...
Paidithalli is a monster.
He doesn’t know anything
about the outside world.
I know how the world works.
You guys don’t know me at all.
None of you do.
I smoke a cigarette and
throw it in uncle’s balcony.
Every day!
I have a few drinks and grow
money plants in those bottles.
Did you know that?
No, you don’t!
I like her.
I like Nandu.
You don’t know that.
I don’t want to get married to Amulya.
None of you even
bothered to ask.
And no one’s ready to listen.
You always complained about me
not expressing myself, right?
Here I am, expressing myself.
Hear me out.
It’s my mother’s wealth.
And she’s my girl.
I only have to go.
Son…
You’d be humiliated if I hit
you, uncle.
Bantu...
Kasiram's daughter is kidnapped.
They are demanding
company shares.
They are asking for Raju.
They'll kill him.
-Please do something.
-I've no connection with that house.
Bantu! listen to me.
I thought you’re my savior.
But you’re also hitting me.
I’ve had a bad day so far.
What happened?
When my brother-in-law heard the good
news about Bantu getting kicked out…
he decided to settle two things.
Mr. Chalapathi Rao didn't
agree to sell his farm.
He decided to threaten him.
He wanted to kidnap your girl
and manipulate you
for the share.
My nephew was drinking.
Few goons were playing
the game, "Tiger and the Goat."
We were going to receive 500
crores worth shares in 15 minutes.
Our men were looking at the road,
hoping this would change their lives.
Brother-in-law was
preparing barbecue.
Everything was going
to plan until then.
But at the same time…
a tiger has arrived.
The goat died.
He's a miracle worker
He is strong willed
He sorts things around the city
He doesn't give up no matter what
He pulled the bull's horns
And played a tune with them
When everyone was terrified of the demon
Like banyan's benches
He challenged the devil for a face off
When there was a monster
At the carnival teasing girls…
He set his ways straight
for a lifetime
There were no knives in it.
None of our men either.
When a bunch of boys were
Drowning in the flood
He swam against the stream
And pulled them ashore
He will show up wherever you dare him to
be
He will make sure you
Don't return in one piece
What about your brother-in-law?
Even if it's a hundred-pound fish...
He will drag it to the
Shore single-handedly
His glance speaks volumes of his valor
He makes the ground beneath you
Tremble with fear
He's a miracle worker
A man of wonders from the North
He poked me with his mischievous gaze
When he makes her feel safe
From a bunch of rogues
You can see a sparkle in her eyes
It's okay.
I’ll take you to the hospital.
When you had the
intention to go…
why’d you tell your father
you had nothing to do with us?
Only during war…
everyone in the country unites despite
their religion, caste and region.
Similarly,
only during tough times…
everyone in the
family comes together.
Despite their selfishness,
hatred and revenge.
That is why I left this
family during a tough time.
If he asked why they should sacrifice
their wealth for her nephew…
or if she said it’s her wealth
and that he is compelled to sign.
These papers wouldn’t
have been signed.
They signed them because
they agreed on something.
After knowing, he gave up half
of his company for his daughter?
How can Kasiram hate
his brother-in-law?
You wanted to see Raj get
furious and die a happy man.
I made it happen and you
didn’t have to die either.
It was hard for me to say I
have nothing to do with this family.
But it was more important
for you guys to be a family.
My King is happy
just like I hoped.
You can continue to visit
your Prince every day.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Do you have anything else to
say, Valmiki?
Nothing much, sir.
If my son said
anything to hurt you…
kindly forgive him. That’s it.
That’s it?
That’s it, sir.
What?
That’s it, Valmiki?
That’s it?
He’s my grandson.
My blood.
My heir.
Can you hear me?
How can you take him
away and say that’s it?
I heard the nurse talk
to him in the hospital.
Son-in-law, he’s your son.
The heir to my fortune.
I provoked the doctor
because I knew the truth.
I let him into the house.
This house, wealth,
his mother and father…
I was wondering if he’d say
the truth to claim any of it.
But he didn’t.
My blood’s boiling ever since
I found out what he’s done.
How come you’re not furious?
No reason to be, sir.
God has punished him already.
The cramp in his leg
soon turned into a limp.
The joy of exchanging kids
soon turned into fear.
He hasn’t had a peaceful
night in the past 25 years.
Let him go, sir.
You’re not angry with any of us.
You’re not greedy
for this wealth.
Why did you come
to this house then?
It’s not only the parents that
wish for their kids’ happiness.
Kids wish for their
parents’ happiness as well.
When I found out they were my
parents after 25 long years…
when I realized they were
going through tough times…
how can I just stand
there and do nothing?
I would never do that, sir.
Everyone who cursed my
dad behind his back…
should touch his feet
when everyone is watching.
My mom should be his
best friend in the world.
He shouldn’t blame himself
for failing his son.
Ramachandra is an
epitome of success.
He can never lose
and I won’t let him.
That is why I came back
and did what I had to.
I don’t need anything
more than this, sir.
Didn’t I tell you,
father-in-law?
Didn’t I?
Didn’t I tell you
how my son would be?
He would be just like him.
Just like him!
Just like him.
Sir, calm down.
Calm down.
Calm down, Dad.
Once…
Once more.
Please calm down, father.
Come.
Let’s meet Yasu.
Father-in-law,
we should tell her the truth.
We should tell her right away.
She will be happy.
-Come!
-No, sir.
No… listen to me.
25 years ago, he made the mistake of
taking two kids away from their mothers.
After nurturing
Raj for 25 years...
you can’t take him away from
her and make the same mistake.
No, sir.
Let’s not correct this mistake.
Let’s leave it here.
God will look after the rest.
You are the truth
that I don't like.
Because you are
better than my son.
I can't leave you...
but today you saved him.
Everything went well.
Otherwise,
I would have lost him.
Women accept complete
strangers as their husbands.
But they don’t accept a son
they haven’t given birth to.
I considered you my son the moment
you went there in his place.
Do I still have to accept you?
I can never repay you for
everything you have done.
I’m returning what you
just brought to us.
Take it.
I didn’t do it expecting
something in return, ma’am.
Please don't do this.
Take it.
A son should accept everything
his mother gives him.
-Did I do the right thing, Dad?
-Yes, dear.
Whatever you do is
the right thing.
Did anyone ever ridicule Ramu
for staying with his in-laws?
Do you know why?
Because your grandpa
requested him to come home.
Similarly, no one should
call you Ramachandra’s son.
Father…
Yasu…
I take back what I said the other day.
That he was born a Prince.
Let him climb his
way up to the top.
Get him a job and
a place to stay.
Why do you look dull, Valmiki?
Aren't half of the assets
enough for your son?
Shall I give him everything?
Train Raj in the same
way as you trained Bantu.
He should become the
CEO in five years.
Do you like it?
We got it, bro.
What are they doing here?
Bantu introduced us.
So, he rubbed his
bad luck onto you.
What is that?
It belongs to brother.
I have a place assigned to me
by the company, uncle.
And we got our stuff as well.
Dear, you belong to the palace.
It hurts me to see you here.
Work hard for five to six
months and prove your worth.
You should become the next CEO.
You should go back
to that house.
What are you talking
about, uncle?
I’m just beginning to relax.
Auntie made me an omelet.
I’m drinking and smoking without
having to worry about it.
And this atmosphere...
feels just like home.
Dear, I can’t catch up.
Can you repeat it
with better grammar?
That is why I wrote this down.
25 years ago, when we were born…
we wouldn’t have had
a problem with this crime.
You should've put me in auntie’s
ward and Bantu in my mom’s ward.
It would’ve been perfect.
It’s a sin, dear.
We can’t take peoples'
fate into our hands.
It wouldn't have worked out.
Tear that paper.
Sir! What are you doing here?
Someone stabbed Appala Naidu
and thrashed his son.
So, they got scared and
withdrew all their cases.
I wanted to give the
good news to Mr. ARK.
I’m the one who stabbed
and thrashed his son, sir.
Hey! Hey!
Don’t claim that you’ve stabbed
everyone in the world.
Give some credit to
the other criminals.
I'm telling the truth, sir.
What do you do for a living?
God, I hate this.
No one believes me
unless I wear this.
Show me your card.
Hold it carefully.
No matter how critical
the emergency is…
I swear I will never
visit your hospital.
Sir… my card.
You’ve given the helicopter
to my son-in-law anyway.
It would be great if you
give me your old Rolls Royce.
Don’t return the petrol bill to
them, please.
Why are you crying?
I didn’t know it’s so hard
to see your dreams come true.
Are you talking about him?
Then you’re right.
They give him a suit to wear.
A girl to marry.
And a helicopter to fly in.
How can they be so happy after handing
over such a huge company to him?
I’ve been blabbering.
Don’t you have something to say?
Well... I was forced to do this.
Give me my card, sir.
I’ll leave.
Wait... go!
I just realized why we all
need a break.
Finally!